Guide to the Mandy Carter Papers, 1970-2013 RL.00195
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Gigs and Events Series, 1979-2013, 108 boxes
  - 7th Biannual Southern Human Rights Organizers' Conference, RTP, N.C., 2008 Dec. 12-14 (Box 207)
  - Out & Equal Planning Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2009 Jan. 7 (Box 207)
  - Immigrant Retreat Planning Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2009 Jan. 8 (Box 207)
  - Progressive Democrats of North Carolina Retreat, Winston-Salem, N.C., 2009 Jan. 10 (Box 207)
  - Presidential Appointments Project Call, 2009 Jan. 12 (Box 207)
  - Obama Pride Celebration, Washington, D.C., 2009 Jan. 18 (Box 207)
  - Obama Inauguration, Washington, D.C., 2009 Jan. 19-20, 2 folders (Box 207)
  - Call with Yvonne Welbon Re: Bennett College, 2009 Jan. 27 (Box 207)
  - Immigrant Justice Retreat Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2009 Jan. 28 (Box 207)
  - LGBT Aging Brekfast, Charlotte, N.C., 2009 Feb. 5 (Box 207)
  - Q-Notes Meeting, Charlotte, N.C., 2009 Feb. 5 (Box 207)
  - Final Immigration Retreat Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2009 Feb. 6 (Box 207)
  - Dinner Meeting with Yvonne Welbon, Greensboro, N.C., 2009 Feb. 7 (Box 207)
  - Lauren Interview, Durham, N.C., 2009 Feb. 10 (Box 207)
  - Duke OUTLaw's Marriage Equality Speaker, Durham, N.C., 2009 Feb. 12 (Box 207)
  - Immigrants Justice Movement Retreat, Greensboro, N.C., 2009 Feb. 12-13 (Box 207)
  - Nancy Kates Bennett Singer Call, 2009 Feb. 17 (Box 207)
  - Temekka Clear Call, Out Like Us, 2009 Feb. 17 (Box 207)
  - United "Let's Talk" 1st Event, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2009 Feb. 17 (Box 207)
  - Immigrant Justice Durham Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2009 Feb. 18 (Box 207)
  - Mab's 60th Birthday, Atlanta, Ga., 2009 Feb. 21 (Box 207)
  - NCCU Colors Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2009 Feb. 23 (Box 207)
  - Census Parternship Meeting at NGLTF Call, 2009 Feb. 24 (Box 207)
  - Windcall Conference Call, 2009 Feb. 25 (Box 207)
  - Call with Sarah Lowman Re: LGBT & Aging, 2009 Mar. 3 (Box 207)
  - Honoring Our Allies 1st Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2009 Mar. 5 (Box 207)
  - 2009 Women's ACC Tournament, Greensboro, N.C., 2009 Mar. 5-8 (Box 207)
  - Out Like Us Meeting, Winston-Salem, N.C., 2009 Mar. 9 (Box 207)
  - Iowa Marriage Equality Speaking Gig, Des Moines, Ia., 2009 Mar. 11-15, 6 folders (Box 207-208)
  - Equality NC Lobby Day, Raleigh, N.C., 2009 Mar. 24 (Box 208)
  - NBJC Black Church Summit National Town Meeting, San Francisco, Calif., 2009 Mar. 27-28 (Box 208)
  - Maud's Reunion Meeting, San Francisco, Calif., 2009 Mar. 29 (Box 208)
  - Honoring Our Elders--2nd Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2009 Mar. 31 (Box 208)
  - BJ Thomas Advocacy Round Table Show, 2009 Apr. 1 (Box 208)
  - Infinity Diamond Women's Conference, Durham, N.C., 2009 Apr. 2-4 (Box 208)
  - Unity 2009 Conference, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2009 Apr. 3-5 (Box 208)
  - 1st Bennett Belles Recognizing Individuality, Diverisity and Equality (BRIDE) Meeting, Greensboro, N.C., 2009 Apr. 9 (Box 208)
  - Rainbow Families Conference, Minneapolis, Minn., 2009 Apr. 17-18 (Box 208)
  - 2009 Beach Week, Nags Head, N.C., 2009 Apr. 18-25 (Box 208)
  - Out Front Minnesota, St. Paul, Minn., 2009 Apr. 21-13 (Box 208)
  - UM Duluth, Duluth, Minn., 2009 Apr. 20 (Box 209)
  - Minnesota Trip, Miscellaneous (Box 209)
  - Western Carolina University, Cullowhee, N.C., 2009 Apr. 24-30 (Box 209)
  - Vance County Group Meeting, 2009 May 2 (Box 209)
  - YWCA Series Planning Meeting, Hillsborough, N.C., 2009 May 4 (Box 209)
  - Meeting with Coleman and Clare re: WRL Asheville, Durham, N.C., 2009 May 5 (Box 209)
  - Queers for Economic Justice/SONG/Audre Lorde Project Conference Call, 2009 May 6 (Box 209)
  - Betsy Crites Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2009 May 11 (Box 209)
  - Interview with Alexis, Durham, N.C., 2009 May 12 (Box 209)
  - Dallas Meeting, Dallas, Tex., 2009 May 15-17 (Box 209)
  - Durham Democratic Women Meeting: A Conversation with Mandy Carter, Durham, N.C., 2009 May 21 (Box 209)
  - Valerie Johnson Meeting, Bennett College, Durham, N.C., 2009 May 22 (Box 209)
  - Interview Lenny Cicero, Durham, N.C., 2009 May 27 (Box 209)
  - NGLTF @ Penn Center, St. Helena Island, S.C., 2009 May 31-June 3, 2 folders (Box 209)
  - Weekend Trip Visit Brenda & Pacita, Sicklerville, N.J., 2009 June 5-7 (Box 209)
  - YWCA Panel Meredith College, Raleigh, N.C., 2009 June 9 (Box 209)
  - NBJC 2nd Annual Unity for Equality, Washington, D.C., 2009 June 17 (Box 209)
  - Call with Cece re: HRC Carolina's Dinner, 2009 June 17 (Box 209)
  - Brown Bag Lunch Meeting with Interns, Democracy North Carolina, Durham, N.C., 2009 June 18 (Box 209)
  - OLOC Southern Regional Gathering, Columbia, S.C., 2009 June 17-19, 2 folders (Box 209)
  - Heirs Project Panel, Durham, N.C., 2009 July 25 (Box 209)
  - NABWMT Convention, Philadelphia, Pa., 2009 July 29-Aug. 2 (Box 209)
  - Keynote Address NABWMT, Philadelphia, Pa., 2009 July 30 (Box 210)
  - 2nd Pacita/Brenda Visit, Sicklerville, N.J., 2009 July 31-Aug. 1 (Box 210)
  - Call with Bishop Rawls, 2009 Aug. 10 (Box 210)
  - 2nd Court Date for James, Durham, N.C., 2009 Aug. 11 (Box 210)
  - YWCA Session--Meredith College, Raleigh, N.C., 2009 Aug. 11 (Box 210)
  - Call with Michelle Rosza--CNN Re: 2010 "Jay in America", 2009 Aug. 12 (Box 210)
  - 14th Annual Gay Lesbian Film Festival, Durham, N.C., 2009 Aug. 13-16 (Box 210)
  - Heirs Project Gala, Carrboro, N.C., 2009 Aug. 16 (Box 210)
  - Durham City Coucil Resolution Vote Same-Sex marriage, Durham, N.C., 2009 Aug. 17 (Box 210)
  - Brian Bond Call re: Pam Spaulding, 2009 Aug. 18 (Box 210)
  - Call with Soda, 2009 Aug. 19 (Box 210)
  - NBJC RAC Call, 2009 Aug. 19 (Box 210)
  - Durham People's Alliance House Party, Durham, N.C., 2009 Aug. 23 (Box 210)
  - NBJC RAC Call re: Black Church Summit 2010, 2009 Aug. 24 (Box 210)
  - Priscilla Meeting--School Supplies Dropoff, Raleigh, N.C., 2009 Aug. 25 (Box 210)
  - Coffee with Liza, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2009 Aug. 26 (Box 210)
  - Call with Kuukua--PSR Gig, 2009 Aug. 27 (Box 210)
  - 3rd SBGA Summit, Atlanta, Ga., 2009 Sept. 5 (Box 210)
  - Final YWCA Session, Raleigh, N.C., 2009 Sept. 8 (Box 210)
  - Call Southern Black Church Summit, 2009 Sept. 10 (Box 210)
  - Call Trans Justice Summit, 2009 Sept. 10 (Box 210)
  - 20th SC Pride Weekend, Columbia, S.C., 2009 Sept. 11-13 (Box 210)
  - AADP Panel Planning Meeting, Raleigh, N.C., 2009 Sept. 17 (Box 210)
  - Equality Alabama, Day of Equality, Birmingham, Ala., 2009 Sept. 18-20 (Box 210)
  - 2nd Coleman, Clare Meeting, Ford Dobbs, N.C., 2009 Sept. 23 (Box 210)
  - Call, Southern Black Church Summit, 2009 Sept. 24 (Box 210)
  - Call, Trans Justice Summit, 2009 Sept. 24 (Box 210)
  - Stone Circles Day of Conversation, Mebane, N.C., 2009 Sept. 25 (Box 210)
  - Election Training, Durham BoE, Durham, N.C., 2009 Sept. 28 (Box 210)
  - "Out in Silence" Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2009 Sept. 30 (Box 210)
  - Call with Steve Vadd re: Nonviolent Network Reunion 2010, 2009 Oct. 2 (Box 210)
  - Call with Dave Glick, 2009 Oct. 2 (Box 210)
  - Call re: Maat Dolpim Visit 2010, 2009 Oct. 4 (Box 211)
  - National Coming Out Day, Minneapolis, Minn., 2009 Oct. 7-11 (Box 211)
  - Southwest MN State University, Marshall, Minn., 2009 Oct. 7 (Box 211)
  - People of Faith Press Conference, St. Paul, Minn., 2009 Oct. 8 (Box 211)
  - General Mills Luncheon Pfund Racial Equity Dinner, Minneapolis, Minn., 2009 Oct. 9 (Box 211)
  - Moving Marriage Equality in Minnesota, Minneapolis, Minn., 2009 Oct. 10 (Box 211)
  - National Coming Out Day Sermon, All God's Children MCC, Minneapolis, Minn., 2009 Oct. 11 (Box 211)
  - YWCA Videotaping, Raleigh, N.C., 2009 Oct. 13 (Box 211)
  - NC Waste Awareness & Reduction Network (WARN) CD Training Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2009 Oct. 14 (Box 211)
  - 2nd Ioka Trip, Postponed until Spring 2010?, Des Moines, Ia., 2009 Oct. 15-22 (Box 211)
  - Seven Sisters Lez Unite Unity Ball, Durham, N.C., 2009 Oct. 17 (Box 211)
  - YWCA Saks 5th Avenue Reception, Raleigh, N.C., 2009 Oct. 20 (Box 211)
  - The Dallas Principles Panel Meeting for Equality NC Conference, Durham, N.C., 2009 Oct. 20 (Box 211)
  - 2nd CD Strategy Meeting, NC WARN Office, Durham, N.C., 2009 Oct. 21 (Box 211)
  - NC WARN Coalition Monitor Training, Raleigh, N.C., 2009 Oct. 22 (Box 211)
  - NC WARN March, CD Action, Raleigh, N.C., 2009 Oct. 24 (Box 211)
  - 1st Blue Cross Blue Shield Spectrum Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2009 Oct. 28 (Box 211)
  - NC WARN Debriefing Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2009 Oct. 30 (Box 211)
  - AARP Panel Call, 2009 Nov. 2 (Box 211)
  - Durham General Election, Durham, N.C., 2009 Nov. 3 (Box 211)
  - Call with Rebecca Voekle Re: Faith Institute CC 2010, Dallas, Texas, 2009 Nov. 4 (Box 211)
  - YWCA Women of Distinction Award, Raleigh, N.C., 2009 Nov. 4 (Box 211)
  - Chicago Black-Brown Summit, Chicago, Ill., 2009 Nov. 6-8 (Box 211)
  - NC WARN Lunch Meeting with Pete & Tim, Durham, N.C., 2009 Nov. 11 (Box 211)
  - NC WARN Meeting- "Next Steps", Durham, N.C., 2009 Nov. 12 (Box 211)
  - Equality NC Conference & Gala, Greensboro, N.C., 2009 Nov. 14, 3 folders (Box 211)
  - Gay in America Panel, North Carolina Central University, Durham, N.C., 2009 Dec. 1 (Box 211)
  - Call with Jan Griesinger, OLOC, 2009 Dec. 1 (Box 211)
  - Phone Interview, Steve McKiernan, 2009 Dec. 3 (Box 211)
  - "Meet the NC WARN Board" Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2009 Dec. 10 (Box 211)
  - Call with Glyn: University of Richmond, 2009 Dec. 11 (Box 211)
  - 2nd Call with Tyie and Blanche--Maat Dompin, 2009 Dec. 13 (Box 211)
  - Radio Interview with Al & Zak WUNC, 2009 Dec. 15 (Box 211)
  - Call with Freedom Center… Board Re: Trans Faith Summit 2010, 2009 Dec. 15 (Box 211)
  - Call with Gordy Stevens, 2009 Dec. 16 (Box 211)
  - Call with Karen Taylor--SAGE, 2009 Dec. 16 (Box 211)
  - Call with Mary Ann Adams re: OLOC, 2009 Dec. 16 (Box 211)
  - Call with Jim Sander re: NC WARN, 2009 Dec. 16 (Box 211)
  - Call with Lashelle Ward re: Womyn's Week Church of Holy Spirit, 2009 Dec. 16 (Box 211)
  - Shades of Pride Meeting, North Carolina Central University, Durham, N.C., 2010 Jan. 4 (Box 212)
  - Faith Institute Retreat, Washington, D.C., 2010 Jan. 6-7 (Box 212)
  - Shades of Pride Board Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2010 Jan. 9 (Box 212)
  - NC WARN Board Meeting, 2010 Jan. 22 (Box 212)
  - Kip & Rubin Highlander Radical Minds Retreat, New Market, Tenn., 2010 Jan. 22-27 (Box 212)
  - Brother Outsider NCCU Shades of Pride Table, Durham, N.C., 2010 Feb. 2 (Box 212)
  - CC 2010, Dallas, Tex., 2010 Feb. 3-7 (Box 212)
  - Racial Justice Institutes Plenary, Dallas, Tex., 2010 Feb. 3 (Box 212)
  - Empowering People of Faith, Dallas, Tex., 2010 Feb. 4 (Box 212)
  - Act on Priniciples Session, Dallas, Tex., 2010 Feb. 5 (Box 212)
  - Organzing as Intersections of Faith and Race, Dallas, Tex., 2010 Feb. 6 (Box 212)
  - Are we a Market or Movement?, Dallas, Tex., 2010 Feb. 6 (Box 212)
  - Black History Event White House, Washington, D.C., 2010 Feb. 10 (Box 212)
  - Freedom Center for Social Justice (FCSJ) Meeting, Charlotte, N.C., 2010 Feb. 13 (Box 212)
  - University of Richmond, Richmond, Va., 2010 Feb. 26-27 (Box 212)
  - Brown-Bag Lunch, Bayard Rustin, University of Richmond, Richmond, Va., 2010 Feb. 26 (Box 212)
  - Keynote Address, "Community Organizing and the Long Arc of Change", University of Richmond, Richmond, Va., 2010 Feb. 26 (Box 212)
  - Saturday Day-Long Session, University of Richmond, Richmond, Va., 2010 Feb. 27 (Box 212)
  - White House Reception, Women's History Month, Washington, D.C., 2010 Mar. 8 (Box 212)
  - NC WARN Board Meeting, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2010 Mar. 10 (Box 212)
  - Ladyslipper Board Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2010 Mar. 17 (Box 212)
  - Women's Week Kick Off: Church of the Holy Spirit Fellowship, Winston-Salem, N.C., 2010 Mar. 18 (Box 212)
  - Race & LGBT Panel, University of North Carolina at Greensboro, Greensboro, N.C., 2010 Mar. 25 (Box 212)
  - Diversity Luncheon: We are 1 Conference, Raleigh, N.C., 2010 Apr. 10 (Box 212)
  - LGBT Organizing Community Building at Unity Conference 2010, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2010 Apr. 10 (Box 212)
  - NC Public Allies Training, North Carolina Central University, Durham, N.C., 2010 Apr. 16 (Box 212)
  - Interview with Angela DiVeglia, Durham, N.C., 2010 Apr. 29 (Box 212)
  - May 4 Primary Election, Durham, N.C., 2010 May 4 (Box 212)
  - NC WARN Board Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2010 May 12 (Box 212)
  - NC WARN Strategy Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2010 May 21 (Box 213)
  - Durham Central Park Co-Housing, Durham, N.C., 2010 May 23 (Box 213)
  - Area Agency on Aging LGBT Panel, Winston-Salem, N.C., 2010 May 25 (Box 213)
  - Kathe Bev: Mandy Meeting--AARP--NC, Raleigh, N.C., 2010 June 9 (Box 213)
  - OLOC National Gathering, Cleveland, Oh., 2010 June 14-18 (Box 213)
  - Triangle Black Pride 2010, Triangle, N.C., 2010 July 29-Aug. 1 (Box 213)
  - Durham Gay Rights Pioneers: 1981 & 1986 Gay Pride Marches, Durham, N.C., 2010 Aug. 8 (Box 213)
  - 15th Annual NCLGFF, Durham, N.C., 2010 Aug. 12-15 (Box 213)
  - NC Democrat Women Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2010 Aug. 14 (Box 213)
  - "One Nation" Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2010 Aug. 17 (Box 213)
  - Southern Strategy @ Highlander, New Market, Tenn., 2010 Aug. 31, 2 folders (Box 213)
  - SC Pride 2010, Columbia, S.C., 2010 Sept. 4 (Box 213)
  - Southern Anti-Racism Network Sept 23 Planning Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2010 Sept. 15 (Box 214)
  - NCJC "Out on the Hill", Washington, D.C., 2010 Sept. 16 (Box 213)
  - 40th CBCF Legislative Conference, Washington, D.C., 2010 Sept. 17, 2 folders (Box 214)
  - Durham Buses to One Nation Working Together, Oct. 2, Durham, N.C., 2010 Sept. 24 (Box 214)
  - NC Pride Fest 2010, Durham, N.C., 2010 Sept. 25 (Box 214)
  - Elaine Marshall Table, NC Pridefest 2010, Durham, N.C., 2010 Sept. 25 (Box 214)
  - Bus Captains Training Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2010 Sept. 27 (Box 214)
  - San Diego/Southern California Black-Brown Summit, San Diego, Calif., 2010 Oct. 1-3 (Box 214)
  - "One Nation Working Together" Rally, Washington, D.C., 2010 Oct. 2 (Box 214)
  - Mt. Pleasant High School Reunion, Schnectady, N.Y., 2010 Oct. 2 (Box 214)
  - NC NOW State Conference, Fayetteville, N.C., 2010 Oct. 9 (Box 214)
  - University of Alabama--Tuscaloosa, Tuscaloosa, Ala., 2010 Oct. 10-12 (Box 214)
  - "Justice or Just Us" Keynote, Tuscaloosa, Ala., 2010 Oct. 11 (Box 214)
  - LGBT of Raleigh Visit, Raleigh, N.C., 2010 Oct. 14 (Box 214)
  - LGBT Center of Raleigh Award Dinner, Raleigh, N.C., 2010 Oct. 16 (Box 214)
  - LGBT Center "Gay & Gray" Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2010 Oct. 18 (Box 214)
  - NC WARN Open House, Durham, N.C., 2010 Oct. 22 (Box 214)
  - Beyond "It Gets Better" Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2010 Oct. 24 (Box 214)
  - Pre-Election Training, Durham, N.C., 2010 Oct. 25 (Box 214)
  - Midterms General Elections-Per 8, Durham, N.C., 2010 Nov. 2 (Box 214)
  - YWCA Academy of Women Awards, Raleigh, N.C., 2010 Nov. 3 (Box 215)
  - NC WARN Brainstorm Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2010 Nov. 4 (Box 215)
  - 2010 Centralina--Conference on Aging, Charlotte, N.C., 2010 Nov. 4-5 (Box 215)
  - NC WARN Board Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2010 Nov. 10 (Box 215)
  - Services & Advocacy for Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual & Transgender Elders (SAGE) Conference, Opening Plenary, New York, N.Y., 2010 Nov. 11-12 (Box 215)
  - 10th Annual Students of Color Conference, University of Oregon, Eugene, Or., 2010 Nov. 12-14 (Box 215)
  - Song-WRL Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2010 Nov. 28 (Box 215)
  - Blue Print NC Meetings, Raleigh, N.C., 2010 Dec. 3 (Box 215)
  - Eno of Heirs Project Event, Raleigh, N.C., 2010 Dec. 3 (Box 215)
  - ISS 40th Anniversary Party, Durham, N.C., 2010 Dec. 4 (Box 215)
  - Meeting with President Obama, Winston-Salem, N.C., 2010 Dec. 6 (Box 215)
  - Elders Planning Meeting, Raleigh, N.C., 2010 Dec. 7 (Box 215)
  - NC WARN Annual Meeting, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2010 Dec. 11 (Box 215)
  - Out Like Us Last Session, Winston-Salem, N.C., 2010 Dec. 14 (Box 215)
  - Ira Sandperl, Celebration of Life, Menlo Park, Calif., 2013 June 2 (Box 215)
  - National Stonewall Democrats Retreat, 2001 (Box 281)
  - Windcall 1999 (Box 281)
  - NOA, 1994 (Box 281)
  - Women in the Life, Malebox, Real, Out in Black, 1997-1998 (Box 283)
  - Stonewall Cincinnati, 1993 (Box 283)
  - Equal Partners in Faith, 1997 (Box 283)
  - NBGLLF, 1996 (Box 283)
- Administrative Files Series, 1970-2007, 23 boxes
  Includes communications, such as mail, faxes, email, and call slips; contact lists and mailing lists; notes and notebooks; to-do lists; resource lists; biographical materials, such as resumes, photographs, press clippings and publications in which Carter appears; materials related to awards Carter has received; and mixed materials from affinity groups. The bulk of the mixed materials from affinity groups arrived loose and were foldered during processing; they typically include promotional materials, pamphlets, fundraising appeals, updates and reports, promotional materials, and informational packets. Very occasionally they include correspondence of a more personal nature or notes from meetings or events.
  Files were assembled during processing and are arranged chronologically within groupings. Original folder titles have been retained, though loose materials were foldered and labeled during processing.
  In terms of overlap, the communications files and the mixed materials from affinity groups include items related to organizations and projects represented in the Organizations and Major Projects Series, including the Other Organizations Subseries.
  - Communications, 1983-1995 (Box 238)
  - Communications, 1995-1996 (Box 239)
  - Communications, 1995-1997 (Box 240)
  - Communications, 1996-1998 (Box 241)
  - Communications, 1997-1999 (Box 242)
  - Communications, 1999-2002 (Box 243)
  - Communications, 2003-2004 (Box 244)
  - Communications, 2004-2010 (Box 245)
  - Contact and mailing lists, 1986-2002, 10 folders (Box 246)
  - Mixed materials from affinity groups, 1980s, 1 folder (Box 247)
  - Mixed materials from affinity groups, 1990s, 47 folders (Box 247-254)
  - Mixed materials from affinity groups, 2000s, 7 folders (Box 254-255)
  - Bios and resumes, 1996-2009, 4 folders (Box 256)
  - Press clippings, 1985-2005, 14 folders (Box 256-257)
  - Awards, 1993-1996 (Box 257)
  - Books, 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box 257)
  - Photographs, 1970-1990s, 5 folders (Box 257)
  - Mandy's slides--list, 1971 (Box 257)
  - Notes and notebooks, 1986, 1991-1998, 6 folders (Box 258)
  - Call slips and memos, 1990s (Box 259)
  - Media file, 1982-1991 (Box 260)
  - Training workshops, 1993-1995 (Box 260)
  - Resource lists, 1993-1998, 2 folders (Box 260)
  - Inventory of boxes, [1994?] (Box 260)
  - To file, 1994, 2 folders (Box 260)
  - To do lists, 1995 (Box 260)
  - Web surfer, 1995 (Box 260)
  - Ideas file, 1996 (Box 260)
  - AOL info, 1997 (Box 260)
  - Bulletin board, 1999 (Box 260)
  - To do's that can wait, 2006 (Box 260)
  - Files, 2007 (Box 260)
- Subject Files Series, 1986-2005, 4 boxes
  Includes a small set of files related to issues relevant to Carter's activism, including a set of files related to African American politicians and organizations.
  Arranged alphabetically. For the most part, materials were assembled during processing, though the African American files in Box 261 remain in their original order.
  - AIDS and the Arts, 1986-1987 (Box 261)
  - Achtenberg Campaign, 1995 (Box 261)
  - African American files, 1992-1995, 30 folders (Box 261)
  - Book catalogs, 1995 (Box 262)
  - Films/books, 1993-1995 (Box 262)
  - Film/video, 1997-1999 (Box 262)
  - Foundations, 1998 (Box 262)
  - Fundraisers, 1993 (Box 262)
  - Fund appeals, membership, and samples, 1993-2001, 3 folders (Box 262)
  - Gay files, 1980-1982 (Box 262)
  - Gay and lesbian families, 1990s, 6 folders (Box 262-263)
  - Gift catalogs (Box 263)
  - LGBT Media and Products, Ads and Order Forms, 1990s (Box 263)
  - Non-profit management, 2004 (Box 263)
  - North Carolina military bases, 1990s (Box 263)
  - Prides, 1990-1996 (Box 263)
  - Public speaking (Box 263)
  - Queer resources on the net, 1995 (Box 263)
  - School G/L/B, 1994 (Box 263)
  - Separation of church and state--publications and pamphlets, 1990s (Box 263)
  - SIECUS sex survey, 1994 (Box 263)
  - South Africa, 1990 (Box 263)
  - Sports, 1994 (Box 263)
  - Tax info, 1990, 1994 (Box 264)
  - Karen Thompson, 1988-1989 (Box 264)
  - Transgender resources, 2000-2005 (Box 264)
  - Travel, Gay and Lesbian, 1994 (Box 264)
  - War tax resistance, 1991 (Box 264)
  - Women's music, 1992-1994 (Box 264)
  - Youth (Box 264)